{
    "subject": "resource/Sones_GraphDB",
    "predicate": "ontology/license",
    "object": "resource/Affero_General_Public_License",
    "human_readable": "Sones GraphDB is licensed under the Affero General Public License.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9681398272514343,
            "question": "Does the Affero General Public License allow for commercial use of Sones GraphDB?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9275241494178772,
            "question": "How does the Affero General Public License impact the distribution of Sones GraphDB?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9127992987632751,
            "question": "What are the implications of the Affero General Public License for modifications made to Sones GraphDB?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8435502648353577,
            "question": "Under which legal framework is Sones GraphDB licensed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7569710612297058,
            "question": "What type of license is used for Sones GraphDB?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6927789449691772,
            "question": "Are there any limitations on the use of Sones GraphDB under its license?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6496815085411072,
            "question": "Where can I find more information about the Affero General Public License?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5889033675193787,
            "question": "Who can legally use Sones GraphDB?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3574236333370209,
            "question": "What are the terms and conditions associated with using Sones GraphDB?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28645840287208557,
            "question": "Is Sones GraphDB open-source software?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sones GraphDB is licensed under the Affero General Public License.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7735_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the terms and conditions associated with using Sones GraphDB?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7735_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who can legally use Sones GraphDB?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7735_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I find more information about the Affero General Public License?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7735_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7735_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7735_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7735_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7735_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7735_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7735_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7735_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7735_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7735_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7735_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that, according to the documents provided, there are multiple mentions of Sones and their GraphDB database software. In one instance, it specifically states that GraphDB is licensed with the GNU Affero General Public License."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis answer is derived from the information provided in the document where it states, \"German data storage specialists >Sones has open sourced their GraphDB database software. GraphDB runs on Windows, Mac OS X, Linux and other Unix flavors and it licensed with the GNU Affero General Public License.\" This confirms that Sones' GraphDB is indeed licensed under the GNU Affero General Public License."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}